{
    "subject": "resource/Ornella_Barra",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Ornella Barra (born December 1953) is an Italian-born Monegasque businesswoman. A qualified pharmacist, she has been involved in the healthcare industry for her entire career, and is currently Executive Vice President of Walgreens Boots Alliance, Inc. and President and Chief Executive of Global Wholesale and International Retail.  Within Walgreens Boots Alliance, Ornella Barra oversees International Retail, which is part of the Retail Pharmacy International Division, as well as directing the Pharmaceutical Wholesale Division. She has been the partner of the Italian billionaire Stefano Pessina for over 30 years.",
    "human_readable": "Ornella Barra (born December 1953) is an Italian-born Monegasque businesswoman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9183074235916138,
            "question": "Is Ornella Barra known for being a businesswoman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8623430132865906,
            "question": "When was Ornella Barra born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8084778189659119,
            "question": "Where was Ornella Barra born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7206010818481445,
            "question": "What country is Ornella Barra from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7004253268241882,
            "question": "In what year did Ornella Barra's birth occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6818785071372986,
            "question": "What is Ornella Barra's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6470898985862732,
            "question": "Besides Italian, what other nationality does Ornella Barra hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6468653678894043,
            "question": "What is Ornella Barra's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6178433895111084,
            "question": "What is the month of Ornella Barra's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5594478249549866,
            "question": "What can be said about Ornella Barra's background?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ornella Barra (born December 1953) is an Italian-born Monegasque businesswoman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2987_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the month of Ornella Barra's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2987_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ornella Barra's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2987_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides Italian, what other nationality does Ornella Barra hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2987_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2987_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe provided text states: \"Ornella Barra (born December 1953) is an Italian-born Monegasque businesswoman.\"  This directly matches the query. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Ornella Barra (born December 1953) is an Italian-born Monegasque businesswoman. This statement can be found in multiple documents, including files 13.txt, 14.txt, 16.txt, and 80.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement about Ornella Barra, including her birth date and nationalities."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}